ebrandz.com 2018-09-18

# eBrandz™ : Privacy Policy

We take your right to privacy seriously, and want you to feel comfortable using our website. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our service and the choices you have associated with that data. 

Why this policy exists:

This data protection policy ensures eBrandz:

  * Complies with data protection law and follow good practice.
  * Protects the rights of staff, customers and partners.
  * Is open about how it stores and processes individualsâ€™ data.
  * Protects itself from the risks of a data breach.

Data Protection Law:

The Data Protection Act 1998 describes how organisations â€” including Agency Platform â€” must collect, handle and store personal information.

These rules apply regardless of whether data is stored electronically, on paper or on other materials.

To comply with the law, personal information must be collected and used fairly, stored safely and not disclosed unlawfully.

The Data Protection Act is underpinned by eight important principles. These say that personal data must:

  * Be processed fairly and lawfully.
  * Be obtained only for specific, lawful purposes.
  * Be adequate, relevant and not excessive.
  * Be accurate and kept up to date.
  * Not be held for any longer than necessary.
  * Processed in accordance with the rights of data subjects.
  * Be protected in appropriate ways.
  * Not be transferred outside the European Economic Area (EEA), unless that country or territory also ensures an adequate level of protection

We use your data to provide and improve our Services. By using our services, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

1\. Definitions

**_a._ Personal Data:**

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession). 

**_b._ Usage Data:**

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the service or from the service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

**_c._ Cookies:**

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a Userâ€™s device.

**_d._ Data Controller:**

Data Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.

**_e._ Data Processor (or Service Providers):**

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller. We may use the services of various service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

**_f._ Data Subject:**

Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.

**_g._ User:**

The User is the individual using our service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.

2\. Information Collection And Use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our service to you. Below are the different types of data we collect. 

**_a._ Personal Data:**

While using our service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * **Email address.**
  * **First name and last name.**
  * **Phone number.**

**_b._ Cookies and Usage Data:**

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

**_c._ Usage Data:**

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our service or when you access the service by or through a mobile device ("Usage Data") This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data. When you access the service by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

**_d._ Tracking & Cookies Data:**

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our service and hold certain information. Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our service. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

  * **Session Cookies.** We use Session Cookies to operate our service.
  * **Preference Cookies.** We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
  * **Security Cookies.** We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

**_e._ Integration Data:**

When authorizing any of the integrations offered with the service, our code will have access to any data made available by the integrations API. If the integration requires a specific set of permission scopes to be authorized by the user, the API data accessed will also be limited to these scopes.

Data retrieved from certain integrations may be cached for a short period and may be stored on our servers to improve the deliverability of data with the service.

The data obtained from integrations will only be used in the dashboard and reports that you and your users have access to. The data is not used internally or any place that you do not have access to.

3\. Use of Data

We use the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain our service
  * To notify you about changes to our service
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service when you choose to do so.
  * To provide customer support
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our service
  * To monitor the usage of our service
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information.

4\. Retention of Data

We will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

We will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

5\. Transfer Of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to â€” and maintained on â€” computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside Canada or USA and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to Canada and USA and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information

6\. Disclosure Of Data

**_a._ Business Transaction:**

 __If we are involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

**_b._ Disclosure for Law Enforcement:**

Under certain circumstances, we may require to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

**_c._ Legal Requirements:**

We may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend our rights or property
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

7\. Security Of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

8\. "Do Not Track" Signals

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

9\. Your Rights

We aim to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data. Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes. If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us. In certain circumstances, you have the right:

  * To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you
  * To rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurate
  * To request the deletion of Personal Data held about you

You have the right to data portability for the information you provide to us. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it. Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

10\. Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our service ("Service Providers"), to provide the service on our behalf, to perform service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our service is used. These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

**_i._ Google Analytics:**

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. You can opt-out of having made your activity on the service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

**_ii._ Behavioral Remarketing:**

We use remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our service.

**_iii._ Google AdWords **

Google AdWords Remarketing service is provided by Google Inc. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page <http://www.google.com/settings/ads> Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

**_v._ Payments:**

We may provide paid products and/or services within the service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors). We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information. The payment processors we work with are PayPal and Braintree Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at - <https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full> <https://www.braintreepayments.com/legal/braintree-privacy-policy>

11\. Links To Other Sites

Our service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services

12\. Children's Privacy

Our service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children"). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

13\. Changes To This Privacy Policy 

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

14\. Contact Us

If you have any questions, please contact us via email at sales@ebrandz.com
